nafex.com 2019-05-25

# Nafex - Foreign Exchange Simplified!

## PRIVACY POLICY

**Introduction**

Nafex Bureau Private Limited (“ **Company** ”, “ **We** ”, “ **Us** ” and “ **Our** ”) respects the privacy of its users on [www.nafex.com](http://www.nafex.com/) (“ **Website** ”). For the purposes of this User Agreement, the term “ **User(s)** ” and wherever the context so requires “ **You** ”, “ **Your** ”, “ **Yourself** ” shall mean any natural or legal person who accesses or uses the Website and in the event that a natural person is representing a business entity, reference to such terms shall include a reference to the business entity.

We have adopted this privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) to inform You of what information We collect from You on or through the Website, how We collect the information, how We may use it and the steps We take to protect it. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the Terms and Conditions (“ **Agreement** ”).

By using the Website, You unconditionally agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and consent to usage, storage and handling of the information submitted by You in accordance with the terms contained hereunder. If You do not agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not proceed further to use this Website.

**User Information**

We collect Your User Information when You successfully submit information while creating Your account or anytime thereafter. User Information is the data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a person through Short Messaging System (“ **SMS** ”) and / or Email and shall include, but not be limited to Your name, name of Your authorized representative, Your email id, and such other information that You may choose to provide. When You submit User Information on the Website, it shall be deemed that You have granted Us the right to collect, store, process, handle and use such User Information, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

In order to access the Website, You must provide Your name, name of authorized representative, Your phone number, and Your email address. During Your usage of the Website, details given by you __ are collected and stored by Us. We identify You through the User Information including the information that You provide on the Website. It is clarified that We shall not be liable, for any reason whatsoever, for the authenticity of any User Information provided by You to Us. You hereby confirm that the User Information provided by You is and shall continue to be valid, true and accurate to the best of Your knowledge.

Any of the aforesaid User Information that is directly capable of identifying You shall be hereinafter referred to as Personally Identifiable Information.

**Collection of routine information**

Certain information may be collected each time You access or use the Website which is saved in server logs. This information includes IP address used by You to connect to the internet and operating system and browser on/from which You are accessing the Website. It is clarified that these statistics help Us in improving the efficiency of the Website by giving Us information relating to Your use of the Website. Such information may include details of Your last visit to the Website, including time, date and the duration of Your session on the Website. This information is used by Us to understand the broad demographic information for aggregate use of the Website and to improve Your user experience of the Website.

**Data Collection Devices**

We use data collection devices known to collect and store information of Users accessing the Website, including cookies and trackers. This helps Us in improving Your experience on the Website. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the User Information You submit to Us.

**Use of User Information**

User Information provided by You is used by Us for the following purposes:

  1. verifying Your Email address;

  2. facilitating Your use of the Website;

  3. facilitating provision of information relating to services provided by You;

  4. processing Your payment through the secured payment gateway;

  5. communicating Your data and information to the Customers;

  6. personalizing Your experience on the Website; 

  7. communicating Your uploaded rates and charges to the Customer;

  8. sending You important information regarding the Website; 

  9. helping You address trouble- shooting problems; 

  10. providing You with related customer service, at Our discretion; 

  11. conducting internal reviews and data analysis for the Website (e.g., to determine the number of Customers utilizing services from particular User); 

  12. improving the content on the Website; 

  13. prevention of fraud or abuses of the Website;

  14. protecting the integrity of the Website; and

  15. to respond to judicial process and provide information to the RBI or law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.

**Sharing of User Information**

Your User Information, except any Personally Identifiable Information/ Sensitive Personal Data or Information, may be shared with such third parties as are required for facilitating the communication of offers tailored for You and to grow Our business which may include Our affiliates, strategic partners, investors, suppliers, and service providers as the case maybe. 

The User Information may be saved in servers in or outside India, at Our sole discretion. 

Except as provided herein, We shall specifically disclose Your User Information including Your Personally Identifiable Information/ Sensitive Personal Data or Information in circumstances where: 

        1. You provided instructions or consent towards such disclosure, by signing a contract, uploading any files, or giving explicit permission to do so; 

        2. We in good faith believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental or regulatory request; (b) enforce the applicable Agreement or Privacy Policy; (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of the Company, its Users or the public as required or permitted by law; and

        3. The User Information that We collect may also be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including any transfers made as a part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of the Company or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or change of ownership or control.

**Security Precautions**

To prevent any form of unlawful interception or misuse of User Information, We use reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the User Information collected. We use reasonable secure and technologically appropriate measures, in compliance with the Information Technology Act, 2000 and the rules related thereto to protect You against loss or misuse of Your User Information including internal reviews of data collection, storage and processing practices and other reasonable security measures which are equivalent to security measures that We use to protect Our own confidential information. However, as You are aware, no online application or website is free of security risks and We do not make any representation in respect of the same. 

We do not warrant that Our Website or any electronic communication made by Us or Customers or any parties, their affiliates and/or other third parties is free from virus or other harmful effects. In the event of any errors in transmission or due to an act of a third party, We shall have no liability. You explicitly agree that Your use of this Website, information and/or services is at Your own individual risk. You agree and confirm that Your User Information may be transferred, processed and stored across national and international borders. You hereby confirm that You have been made aware of the security measures undertaken by Us and You expressly consent to Us storing, handling, using Your User Information.

**Links to other third party sites**

The Website may provide third party information and links to other websites or applications that are not affiliates of or operated or controlled by Us including but not limited to advertisements and/or facilities that You access from the Website (“ **External Links** ”). However, We are not responsible for any form of transmission, whatsoever, received by You from any External Link and accordingly do not make any representations concerning the privacy practices or other policies of the providers of such External Links or External Entities. Under no circumstances shall the Company be deemed to control or guarantee the accuracy, integrity, or quality of the information, data, text, software, sound, photographs, graphics, videos, cookies, messages or other materials available on or through such External Links. Any User Information provided by You to such External Links shall be governed in accordance with the privacy policies of such External Links and it is recommended that You review their privacy policy prior to providing any information thereto. 

**Change in Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to update, modify and amend any of the terms of Our Privacy Policy, at any time without prior intimation to You. We will post these changes on the Website. These changes will become effective immediately on posting. We shall not be liable for any failure or negligence on Your part to review the updated Privacy Policy before accessing or using the Website. Your continued use of the Website, following changes to the Privacy Policy, will constitute Your acceptance of those changes. 

**Force Majeure**

Notwithstanding anything contained in this Privacy Policy or elsewhere, We shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of Your User Information, if such loss, damage or misuse is attributable to a Force Majeure Event. " **Force Majeure Event** " shall mean any event that is beyond Our reasonable control and shall include, without limitation, sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, network errors, computer hacking, technical snags, unauthorized access to computer data and storage device, breach of security and encryption and any other like event beyond Our control.

**Contacting Grievance Officer**

If You have any questions about (i) this Privacy Policy; (ii) practices pertaining to the Application, or (iii) Your dealings with this Website or believe that We have not adhered to the terms of this Privacy Policy, You may contact the Grievance Officer of the Company at:

Name :

| 

Kiran S  
  
---|---  
  
Phone :

| 

+91 90660 02013  
  
Email :

| 

kiran@nafex.com
